<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Anthony Rumsey]]></title>
  <link href="http://me.planetrumsey.ca/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://me.planetrumsey.ca/"/>
  <updated>2014-06-18T13:55:20-04:00</updated>
  <id>http://me.planetrumsey.ca/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Anthony Rumsey]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Delivering Managed Content to Your Native Apps]]></title>
    <link href="http://me.planetrumsey.ca/blog/2014/05/16/delivering-managed-content-to-your-native-apps/"/>
    <updated>2014-05-16T14:16:55-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://me.planetrumsey.ca/blog/2014/05/16/delivering-managed-content-to-your-native-apps</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://www.connectcon.ch/2014/en.html">CONNECT Web Experience (previously CQCON)</a> is a month away, and I&rsquo;m excited to be attending this event to talk about <a href="http://www.connectcon.ch/2014/en/speakers2/anthony-rumsey.html">Delivering Managed Content to Native Apps</a>.</p>

<p>With the release of AEM 6.0 the ability to leverage its powerful web content management tools with the cross-platform app development platform provided by Phonegap Enterprise is now available. The result is the ability for an organization to quickly deliver an improved app experience across all their segments at a reduced cost.</p>

<p>In many cases however organizations with an existing mobile app presence have most likely already spent considerable time and money on developing native app solutions.  Over time these native apps start to grow larger and become harder to easily deliver updated content simultaneously across multiple platforms.  Furthermore, more often the marketing organization demands the ability to deliver the brand message directly to their mobile properties.  While these apps may not be in a position to move completely to the use of web technologies and cross-platform development provided by Phonegap, the power of AEM apps can still be integrated directly into an existing native app.</p>

<p>In my developer focused presentation I will cover in detail how content created with AEM apps can then be included in an existing native app. Starting with a native Android project I will show the process of integrating AEM generated content and highlight how content in the app can be updated without any further native development being required. Finally, I will also demonstrate the ability for AEM content to communicate with the rest of the native application.</p>

<p>CONNECT WebEx is shaping up to be the essential event for anyone working with Adobe Experience Manager. I look forward to seeing you all there!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
